<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interesting Stuff on Joseph Carlson</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/interesting-stuff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interesting Stuff on Joseph Carlson</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/interesting-stuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fixing MacOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interesting-stuff/fixing-macos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interesting-stuff/fixing-macos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the years, I have shifted between Windows, Linux, and MacOS for my daily use operating system. Originally, it was Windows 10, then MacOS, then Ubuntu, then Windows 11, then Fedora, and lastly, MacOS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The honest reason why I switched to Mac? I spent so much fixing Windows at Technician X, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t bear the idea of coming home to the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong. Windows is great in enterprise environments. Compatibility is king. But I have found that MacOS is a far more pleasant operating system to use after some essential utilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right to Repair</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interesting-stuff/right-to-repair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interesting-stuff/right-to-repair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shoutout to &lt;a href=&#34;https://futo.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&#xA;  FUTO&#xA;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://consumerrights.wiki/Main_Page&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&#xA;  CATF (Consumer Action Task Force Wiki)&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been a long-time subscriber of Louis Rossmann&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel for his outspoken stance on the consumer right to repair, and more recently, consumer rights across all industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With his online media presence, Louis Rossmann has brought FUTO into the spotlight to support the development of new and existing technologies that provide alternatives to products developed by big tech. You can read more about it here:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
